we've been given some code that raises
an
error so on line one you can see that we
have an array
names and this array contains four names
on line two it looks like we're trying
to replace the name margaret with the
name
jody however this is the line of code
that's going to raise an
error it appears that what we're trying
to do
is use the array assignment method
however we've passed in an
element of the array the string margaret
rather than the index of that element
when we use array element reference
or element assignment we need to place
the index
of the element in the square brackets
not the element itself
so the index of the string margaret is
three
this is a four element array and the
index is zero based
so now on line two we are reassigning
the element at index three
to the string jody i'm going to
output the names array and run this code
we'll still expect to see a four element
array but now the last element will be
jody
rather than margaret
and that's what we see